cashmylinks.com 2016-06-25

# CashMyLinks - Privacy Policy Page

**Privacy Policy**  
CashMyLinks is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using any of our online services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we receive when you transmit data to any machine owned by CashMyLinks.  

**Web Form Information**  
When you submit information to CashMyLinks to open an account, we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, email address, phone number. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen.  

**Web Site Usage Information**  
We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you access any of our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our Web sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each web page, and the length of their visits.

**How We Use Information Collected**  
We may use the collected information in the following ways: 

  * To register you as a affiliate with us and establish an account for you.
  * To send you email notifications about our new or existing CashMyLinks products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.
  * To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use (for example to protect our intellectual property rights). We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law may require us to do so.

**Cookies**  
We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our online services. CashMyLinks employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers.

**Security**  
The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary.

**IP Addresses**  
Your visit on the CashMyLinks website(s) will involve the transmission of your Internet protocol address ("IP Address") to CashMyLinks' servers. This IP Address is necessary for communication with you via the Internet and may be used and stored on our servers. We use IP Addresses to determine the general geographic locations of our users. We may also use this information for analytics purposes. 

**Policy Modifications**  
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically.

**Comments and Questions**  
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us Here. You could also write to us P.O. Box 92043 9200 Weston Rd Vaughan, ON, L4H 3J3 Canada
